Pride Center of the Capital Region; Records apap361
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1973-2015; 13.5 cubic ft.
  - Photo of Center Members, Undated (Flat-file 2)
  - Political Candidates Support, Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Presidential Plaque, 1971-1999 (Oversize 9)
  - Pride 2000 (Floppy-disk 11)
  - Pride Center In the News, 1972-1980; 1983-1987; 1990-1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Pride Center In the News, 2010 (Oversize 7, Folder 5)
  - Pride Part 1- Bowling, Undated (Cd 10)
  - Pride.qxd, Pride 1.qxd, and Pride 2.qxd, Undated (Floppy-disk 12)
  - Pride Vendors 1997 (Floppy-disk 13)
  - Prison Sexuality, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Project Equinox/ Refer Switchboard- Budget Cuts, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Property of Love: A Baptist's View of Sexuality and the Bible- Lawrence Can Heusen, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Psychological Association of Northeastern NY Award, 2000 (Oversize 9)
  - Psychological Scaling of Proposed Title IX Guidelines, Undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Quotes from Pride Center Members, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Raffle, 2007 (Oversize 7, Folder 6)
  - Rainbow Heights Club, Undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Ramada Inn-Donation, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Real Sex Ed Saves Lives, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Recognition From Governor Mario M. Cuomo, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Recognition From the White House, 1993; 1995; 2009; 2012-2014 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Recognition- Kristen E. Gillibrand, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Religion in the Gay Community, 1975-1978; 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute (RPI) GLBT Training Packet, Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Rescue Fund- Center Debt, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Roxo Easy CD Creator Update, Undated (Cd 11)
  - Shaw Office Disk 4, Undated (Cd 12)
  - Shaw Office Disk 5, Undated (Cd 13)
  - Unidentified, Undated (Floppy-disk 14)
  - Unidentified, Undated (Floppy-disk 15)
  - Unidentified, 1965-2017 (Floppy-disk 16)
  - Unidentified, Undated (Floppy-disk 17)
  - Welcome Sign, Undated (Oversize 9)
  - Youth Media Project Student Town Meetings, 2009 November 17 (Cd 14)